# NATALIA SOWA

## Web Development Student



ABOUT ME

Being a Full Stack Web Developer is much more creative and enjoyable than I expected it to be. After 4 years working in Marketing field, I've decided to switch paths and persue my dreams. I've started my journey with HackYourFuture school where I got to learn how to create beneficial web solutions using various technologies, such as react, mysql, expressJs etc.

EXPERIENCE

#### **HackYourFuture Graduation Project | Link**

Jan 2022 - Present - 2 months, Copenhagen

Technologies: React JS, Node JS, Storybook, FireBase, Github.

#### **Demant, Commercial Excellence**

Assistant to Manager

Jan 2020 - Dec 2021 - 1 yr 7 mos, Smørum

Hosting of Sales Training Webinars in ISpringLearn. Implementation of the Learning & Knowledge Platform - 'Fuse' with technologies such as Figma, CSS, HTML, JS.

#### Oticon Medical, Marketing & Communication

Student Assistant

Aug 2018 - feb 2021 - 2 yr 7 mos, Smørum

Working with the Marketing Portal (SharePoint). Re-invoicing bi-yearly of translation costs. Assisting with the implementation and launch of a new Digital Asset Management System (DAM).

EDUCATION

#### HackYourFuture, Web Development | Curriculum

7-month coding bootcamp with modules on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL and ReactJS.

2021 - 2022, Copenhagen

#### Aarhus BSS, Bachelor in Economics & Business Administration

2018 - 2021, Aarhus

#### Copenhagen Business Academy, AP in Marketing

2016 - 2018, Copenhagen

#### Contact

+45 91458461

Strandbygade 33, Esbjerg

in Linkedin/Natalia Sowa

GitHub Profile

#### Industry Knowledge

Website Design
Web Development
Benchmarking

#### Tools & Technologies

Figma, Storybook,
HTML, CSS,
VSCode, GIT,
Heroku, jQuery
Swagger, mySQL,
FireBase, Express,
React JS, Node JS,
SharePoint,
ISpringLearn, Fuse

### Languages

Polish (native)
English (professionnal)
Danish (basics)